<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pepper&#39;s Serendipity</title>
    <link>https://pepperf.ink/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pepper&#39;s Serendipity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-zh</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 16:50:50 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pepperf.ink/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum - Agile Development</title>
      <link>https://pepperf.ink/post/manage-scrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 16:50:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepperf.ink/post/manage-scrum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Scrum is one of the most popular ways to implement Agile. In this iterative approach, there are Sprints that last one to two weeks and allow the team to deliver software on regular basis. Scrum uses a software model that follows a set of roles, responsibilities, and meetings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IP-tables.md</title>
      <link>https://pepperf.ink/post/ip-tables/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 09:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepperf.ink/post/ip-tables/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;iptables is a user-space utility program that allows a system administrator to configure the tables provided by the Linux kernel firewall (implemented as different Netfilter modules) and the chains and rules it stores. iptables requires elevated privileges to operate and must be executed by user root.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>健身健美分享会2019年11月09日</title>
      <link>https://pepperf.ink/post/%E5%81%A5%E8%BA%AB%E5%88%86%E4%BA%AB/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 22:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepperf.ink/post/%E5%81%A5%E8%BA%AB%E5%88%86%E4%BA%AB/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;交大第二届健体比赛开始了，本次有幸邀请了陈胄学长来分享他的经验。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export Maven Project with Dependencies</title>
      <link>https://pepperf.ink/post/export-maven-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 13:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepperf.ink/post/export-maven-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We want to export a Java-based project to an executable &lt;code&gt;jar&lt;/code&gt; file. The process to export a &lt;code&gt;jar&lt;/code&gt; file is not the same with a Maven Project which contains external denpendencies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker and Create Images</title>
      <link>https://pepperf.ink/post/docker-usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 11:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepperf.ink/post/docker-usage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Docker is a software platform that allows you to build, test, and deploy applications quickly. In this post, we are going to install Docker and create an image for the test environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop Wearing Others&#39; Shirts</title>
      <link>https://pepperf.ink/post/stop-wearing-others-shirts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 01:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepperf.ink/post/stop-wearing-others-shirts/</guid>
      <description>Though there are 56 ethnic groups in China with extremely different religions and customs, we still consider ourselves as people from a united Chinese culture, facing up to the western mainstream society. Living in a society with rigid protection of diversity, I never realize the severe problem of cultural appropriation until the appearance of surreal oriental images conveyed by European and American artists, filmmakers and producers. Studying alone abroad and receiving directly the news from foreign media confirm my initial suspicions that the absurd way Chinese culture is shown has dramatically distorted the images in people&amp;rsquo;s mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a custom API in WordPress</title>
      <link>https://pepperf.ink/post/add-custom-api-wp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepperf.ink/post/add-custom-api-wp/</guid>
      <description>This post presents a method to create custom API endpoints in WordPress REST API (V2).
WordPress REST API The WordPress REST API provides API endpoints for WordPress data types that allow developers to interact with sites remotely by sending and receiving JSON (JavaScript Object Notation) objects. When you send content to or make a request to the API, the response will be returned in JSON. This enables developers to create, read and update WordPress content from client-side JavaScript or from external applications, even those written in languages beyond PHP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the middle of my summer intern in France</title>
      <link>https://pepperf.ink/post/summer-intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepperf.ink/post/summer-intern/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post on the website
Preface I&amp;rsquo;ve been constructing this website for about two weeks. This post should have been written long time ago. Finally, I got the time to write something about me. I am studying in Télécom ParisTech and it will still take me 1 year. After leaving Paris, I will come back to Shanghai Jiaotong University for another 1 year and a half and obtain my Master Degree.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>