<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Intern on Pepper&#39;s Serendipity</title>
    <link>https://pepperf.ink/tags/intern/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Intern on Pepper&#39;s Serendipity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-zh</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pepperf.ink/tags/intern/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a custom API in WordPress</title>
      <link>https://pepperf.ink/2018/add-custom-api-wp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepperf.ink/2018/add-custom-api-wp/</guid>
      <description>This post presents a method to create custom API endpoints in WordPress REST API (V2).
WordPress REST API The WordPress REST API provides API endpoints for WordPress data types that allow developers to interact with sites remotely by sending and receiving JSON (JavaScript Object Notation) objects. When you send content to or make a request to the API, the response will be returned in JSON. This enables developers to create, read and update WordPress content from client-side JavaScript or from external applications, even those written in languages beyond PHP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the middle of my summer intern in France</title>
      <link>https://pepperf.ink/2018/summer-intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepperf.ink/2018/summer-intern/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post on the website
Preface I&amp;rsquo;ve been constructing this website for about two weeks. This post should have been written long time ago. Finally, I got the time to write something about me. I am studying in Télécom ParisTech and it will still take me 1 year. After leaving Paris, I will come back to Shanghai Jiaotong University for another 1 year and a half and obtain my Master Degree.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>